Finding Aid for the Lewis MacAdams papers LSC.2289
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Writing by MacAdams
  - Journalism (Box 37, Box 38, Box 39, Box 40, Box 41, Box 42, Box 43, Box 44, Box 45, Box 46, Box 47, Box 48, Box 49, Box 50, Box 51, Box 52, Box 53, Box 54, Box 55, Box 56, Box 57)
    - Live!, v. 1, no. 5. Los Angeles., 1996 June (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - LOKA. Boulder., 1975 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - LONGHOUSE, no. 3. Queen Charlotte Islands., 1980 March (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - los angeles. Los Angeles., 2005 July (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Los Angeles Times Magazine, v. 2, no. 5. Los Angeles., 1986 February 2 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - MAGAZINE, v. 13, no. 1. Venice., 1983 Winter (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - MAGAZINE, v. 13, no. 2. Venice., 1983 Spring (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Mag City, no. 7. New York., 1979 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - MAIN, v. 2, no. 2. Venice., 1987 March-April (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - MAIN, v. 2, no. 6. Venice., 1987-1988 December-February (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Media Arts, v. 1, no. 7. Beverly Hills., 1984 Autumn (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - mgur poesia, no. 0. Bologna., 1987 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Miam, no. 1. San Francisco., 1977 May (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Miam, no. 5. San Francisco., 1978 April (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - mini, no. 2. Riva San Vitale., 1986 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - mini, no. 3. Riva San Vitale., 1986 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - mini, no. 4. Riva San Vitale., 1986 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - mini, no. 6. Riva San Vitale., 1986 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Mother Jones, v. 25, issue 6. San Francisco., 2000 November-December (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Mungo vs. Ranger, no. 3. San Francisco., 1999 Fall (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Narachan, no. 3. Germany., 1978 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - The Nassau Lit. Princeton., 1965 Spring (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Neek Magazine. London., 1982 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - New Magazine, v. 8, no. 1. Venice., 1977 January (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - New Blood, v. 1, no. 1. Boulder., 1980 December (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - New Perspectives, v. 1, no. 2. Los Angeles., 1984 Spring (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - New Wilderness Letter, no. 11. New York., 1982 December (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - The New Yorker. New York., 2001 September 24 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Nude Erections, no. 2. Los Angeles., 1985 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Il Nuovo Laboratorio, no. 8-9. Bologna., 1983 November (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - October, no. 8. Cambridge., 1979 Spring (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Oculist Witnesses, no. 1. Dorchester., 1975 Summer (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - ON TV, v. 6, no. 3. Glendale., 1982 June (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - ON TV, v. 6, no. 6. Glendale., 1982 September (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Open Window, no. 2. New York., 1976 Fall (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Or, issue 9. Los Angeles., 2012 Fall (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Other World Poetry Newsletter, v. 1, no. 1. Amsterdam., 1979 July (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Pacific Plate, v. 1, no. 2. Bolinas., 1976-1977 Winter (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - The Paris Review, v. 10, no. 37. Paris., 1966 Spring (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - The Paris Review, v. 12, no. 46. Paris., 1969 Spring (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - The Paris Review, v. 13, no. 51. Paris., 1971 Winter (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Peninsula Magazine, no. 3. Bolinas., 1989 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Penumbra. Turlock., 1999 Spring (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Poetry Flash, no. 59. San Francisco., 1978 January (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Poetry Flash, no. 72. Oakland., 1979 March (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Poetry Information, no. 15. London., 1976 Summer (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Poetry News, no. 3. Venice., 1980 December (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Poetry News, no. 5. Venice., 1981 February (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - The Poetry Project Newsletter, no. 71. New York., 1980 January (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - The Poetry Project Newsletter, no. 72. New York., 1980 February (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - The Poetry Project Newsletter, no. 72. New York., 1980 March (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - The Poetry Project Newsletter, issue 110. New York., 1984 December (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - The Poetry Project Newsletter, issue 126. New York., 1987 April-May (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - The Poetry Project Newsletter, no. 213. New York., 2007 December 2008 January (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Poet's Audio Center catalog. Washington, D.C., 1989 May 1 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Poet's Audio Center catalog. Washington, D.C., 1989 October 15 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Poet's Audio Center catalog. Washington, D.C., 1990 May 1 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Post Script, v. 4, no. 1. Jacksonville., 1984 Fall (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Pressure Drop, no. 2. London., circa 1975 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Printed Matter catalogue, v. 2, no. 1. New York., 1988 Fall (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Q, v. 2, no. 1. London., 1987 October (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Republic Magazine. Los Angeles., 1985 (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Rocky Ledge, no.1. Nederland., 1979 April-May (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Rocky Ledge, no. 2. Nederland., 1979 August-September (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Rocky Ledge, no. 3. Nederland., 1979 November-December (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Rocky Ledge, no. 4. Boulder., 1980 February-March (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Rocky Ledge, no. 5. Boulder., 1980 July-August (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Rocky Ledge, no. 6. Boulder., 1980 October-November (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Rolling Stone, no. 672-3. New York., 1993 December 23-1994 January 6 (Box 8, Folder 5, Box 53, Folder 1)
      Box 8 contains a framed clipping of "A Gathering of the Tribes: A report from the 1993 World Peace and Healing Gathering of the Rainbow Family of Living Light" by MacAdams.
    - Rootdrinker, no. 16. Potsdam., 1989 Summer (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - S Press. Wuppertal., 1981 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - San Francisco Review of Books, v. 2, no. 5. San Francisco., 1976 September (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Saturday Morning, v. 2, no. 1 and 2. New York and London., 1978 Summer (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Soft Need, no. 17. Basel-Paris., 1977 October (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Sparring With Beatnik Ghosts, v. 2, no. 2. Santa Cruz., 2012 February 12 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - St. Mark's Today. Dallas., 1992 July (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Stigmata, no. 14. Paris., 1981 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Stigmata, no. 15. Paris., 1981 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Street Magazine, v. 2, no. 4, issue 8. Port Jefferson., 1978 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Takeokikuchi Quarterly, no. 1. Tokyo., 1988-1989 Autumn-Winter (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Telephone, no. 12. New York., 1976 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Telephone, no. 13. New York., 1977 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Tempo. Taos., 2004 February 12-18 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - The Ten Directions, v. 14, no. 1. Los Angeles., 1993 Spring-Summer (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - The, no. 3. Boulder., 1968 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - The, no. 5. Boulder., 1969 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - The, no. 6. Boulder., circa 1970 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - The, no. 7. Boulder., circa 1971 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - The, no. 14. Boulder., circa 1975 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - This Is Important, no. 11. Los Angeles., 1985 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Tom Veitch Magazine, no. 3. San Francisco., 1971 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Trans Atlantik. Munich., 1984 July 7 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Turkey Buzzard Review, no. 3. Bolinas., 1981 June (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - United Artists Seven, no. 3. Lenox., 1979 June (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Un Poco Loco. New York., 1978 December (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Un Poco Loco. New York., 1979 February (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Un Poco Loco. New York., 1979 April (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Un Poco Loco. New York., 1979 May (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Un Poco Loco. New York., 1979 June (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Un Poco Loco. New York., 1979 July (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Un Poco Loco. New York., 1979 August (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Un Poco Loco. New York., 1979 November (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Un Poco Loco. New York., 1979 December (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - The Vajradhatu Sun, v. 12, no. 6. Boulder., 1990 August-September (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Vanitas, no. 2. New York., 2006 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Variety, v. 224, no. 28. Los Angeles., 1989 July 14 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Venice Magazine, v. 1, no. 2. Venice., 1988 November (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Vintage Guitar Magazine, v. 11, no. 10. Bismarck., 1997 July (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Voice Magazine. Los Angeles., 1989 February (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Voice Magazine. Los Angeles., 1989 June (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Wear, no. 1. Santa Monica., 1985 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Wear. Santa Monica., 1985 October (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Wear, v. 1, no. 4. Santa Monica., 1985 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - WET Magazine, 1976-1981 (Box 55, Box 56)
      Biography/History
      MacAdams was an editor at WET from 1980-1982. Venice-based artist and designer Leonard Koren launched WET: The Magazine of Gourmet Bathing in 1976, an extension of his work creating "bath events" and "unusual bath environments" that began while earning a Master's degree in Architecture and Urban Planning from UCLA in 1972. Koren ceased publication of WET after a five-year run, but continued to create work dedicated to bathing, including a history of his signature magazine titled Making Wet: The Magazine of Gourmet Bathing.
      Scope and Contents
      Issues of WET Magazine from Lewis MacAdams' library that were originally donated with the papers have been individually cataloged in the UCLA Library online catalog. Records for these items may be found by searching the Special Coll/Archive SPAC "LMAC" using the Advanced search tab in the Library catalog, or keyword searching "Books from the Library of Lewis MacAdams."
      Box 39 contains ephemera related to WET, including postcards and bookmarks, and a business card for MacAdams with WET logo.
    - Whole Earth Review, no. 85. Sausalito., 1995 Spring (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Whole Life Times, no. 141. Malibu., 1994 December (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Whole Life Times, v. 26, no. 4. Malibu., 2004 April (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Wind Bell, v. 16, no. 1. San Francisco., 1978-1979 Winter (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - The World, no. 31. New York., 1978 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - Writes of Spring. Bolinas., circa 1987 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - XTRA, v. 2, issue 6. Dallas., 1985 June (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Yolanda Pipeline's Magazine. Boulder and Palo Alto., 2003 Spring (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Film and television projects (Box 58, Box 59, Box 60, Box 61, Box 62, Box 63, Box 64, Box 65, Box 66, Box 67, Box 68, Box 69, Box 70, Box 71, Box 72, Box 73, Box 74, Box 130, Folder 4)
    The film and television projects subseries includes:
    Boxes 58-61: What Happened to Kerouac? materials include scripts, research files, notebooks, correspondence, reviews, posters, and audiovisual materials.
    Box 62-65: Scripts, screen plays, teleplays, drafts, research files, notes, outlines, and critiques for Landslide by Lesley Taplin and MacAdams.
    Box 65, folders 11-12 contain drafts of Banana Republic screenplay by MacAdams and Cheech Marin.
    Box 66 contains audiovisual materials related to In the Garden Ring and Live From the 21st Century.
    Box 67 contains EZTV materials concerning its history, Bogosian's Fun House, and Sushi Ole as well as John Hall Dorr poems 1978-1985.
    Box 68: Billy Rader screenplay drafts.
    Box 69: Only One Swims Away or Man Bites Shark script drafts.
    Box 70: Script drafts, treatments, and notes for China Girl by Lesley Taplin and MacAdams and The Last Days of Hank Williams by Boz Scaggs and MacAdams.
    Box 71: Tokyo script drafts.
    Box 72: Tokyo drafts, correspondence, and a L.A. Sands file.
    Box 73: Files for the following projects: Dark Bob, Black and White, The Rest of the Story (Young Americans), The Legend of the Mexican Kitchen, My Traitor's Heart, They Brought the Water, and Virginia Dare treatment by Lesley Taplin and MacAdams.
    Box 74: Files for various projects including California One, Andrei Toluzakov, History of Rock and Roll, and History of TV.
    Box 130: Kerouac poster mock up board and original print.
    Box 59, folder 12: One audio cassette of Kerouac to Steve Allen Poetry for the Beat Generation plus Kerouac Blues and Haikus.
    Box 60: Three What Happened to Kerouac? U-Matic tapes and two What Happened to Kerouac? VHS.
    Box 64, folder 8: One Landslide meeting audio cassette.
    Box 66: Nine VHS and one U-Matic tape.
    Box 67: Two Eric Bogosian's Fun House VHS.
    Box 73: One Spanish Kitchen VHS.
    Box 74, folder 6: One audio cassette.
    Box 65, folder 11: Four 5.25 inch floppy disks labeled "Banana Republic."
    Box 67, folder 7: One 5.25 inch floppy disk labeled "Bogosian plus Metropix Kerouac."
    Box 68, folder 11: One 5.25 inch floppy disk and six 3.5 inch floppy disks.
    Box 69, folder 4: One 5.25 inch floppy disk.
    Box 72, folder 4: Eight 5.25 inch floppy disks.
    Box 73, folder 1: One 5.25 inch floppy disk labeled "Dark Bob Wiseblood."
    Box 74, folder 4: One History of Rock and Roll 3.5 inch floppy disk.
- Correspondence
  The correspondence series has been organized by the last name of the sender and includes personal and professional letters.
  - A - C (Box 75, Folder 1-6)
    This box includes correspondence from Linda J. Albertano, Lauren Bon, Bill Clinton, and Peter Coyote.
  - D - F (Box 76, Folder 1-8)
    This box includes correspondence from George Drury Smith, Diane Di Prima, John Doe, Lawrence Ferlinghetti, and Raymond Foye.
  - Family - J (Box 77, Box 78, Box 79, Box 80)
    Boxes 77-79 contain files labeled by MacAdams as Family Letters.
    Box 80 includes correspondence from family, Alexandra Garrett, Eric Garcetti, Allen Ginsberg, and Tom Hayden.
  - K - M (Box 81, Folder 1-6)
    This box includes correspondence from Joanne Kyger, the Los Angeles Institute of Contemporary Art (LAICA), Gary Leonard, the Lannan Foundation, and Duncan McNaughton.
    Folder one contains The Hagen Report and photographs of Nina Hagen from the 1980s.
  - M - O (Box 82, Folder 1-8)
    This box includes correspondence from Metropolitan Pictures, Naropa Institute, Harry E. Northup, and Lynn O'Hare.
  - P - Postcards (Box 83, Folder 1-6)
    This box includes correspondence from The Poetry Center and The Poetry Project.
  - Postcards - S (Box 84, Folder 1-5)
    This box includes correspondence from Aram Saroyan.
  - S - W (Box 85, Folder 1-9)
    This box includes correspondence from Stone Press Weekly, Barbara T. Smith, Boz Scaggs, Michelle Shocked, T of R organization, and Southern Methodist University (SMU). The SMU file contains the finding aid for The Papers of Lewis MacAdams (Mss 57).
  - W - Z (Box 86, Folder 1-7)
    This box also includes anonymous correspondence and letters with first names only.
- FoLAR files
  The Friends of the Los Angeles River (FoLAR) series documents the 40-year art project started by MacAdams in 1986 to promote creative solutions and policies to return the Los Angeles River to its original wild state. The materials include original artwork by FoLAR collaborators for publicizing cleanup events, correspondence between MacAdams and local politicians and activists, materials related to the Not A Cornfield project, and photographs and certificates relating to MacAdams environmental activism.
  CONTAINS AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS: This collection contains both processed and unprocessed audiovisual materials. For information about the access status of the material that you are looking for, refer to the Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note at the series and file levels. All requests to access processed audiovisual materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
  - Historic materials (Box 88, Folder 1, Box 87, Folder 1-26)
    Box 87: Files include Meandering publication, L.A. River Org beginning, L.A. River Watershed Botanical Survey, FoLAR questionnaires, FoLAR one sheet, notebooks, and flyers.
    Box 88, folder 1 contains oversize photographs, "Old Man River" profile, and Diane Gamboa's original art work for Gran Limpieza Friends of the Los Angeles River present the great Los Angeles River Clean-Up poster.
  - Correspondence (Box 89, Folder 1-4)
    This box includes correspondence from Diane Gamboa, Eric Garcetti, and Catherine Mulholland.
  - Reports and plans (Box 90, Folder 1-16)
    This box includes the following files: Los Angeles Riverkeepers, City North LA Design Action Planning Team Report, LA River Revitalization Master Plan, FoLAR newsletters, and flood control reports.
  - Not a Cornfield files (Box 91, Folder 1-10)
    This box includes the following files: Cornfield State Park Report, Not a Cornfield, The Los Angeles River: A City Runs Through It, FoLAR, and L.A. River course materials.
    Three VHS tapes.
    Six 3.5" floppy disks.
  - Press and clippings (Box 92, Folder 1-5)
    Materials include periodicals with features on MacAdams, the L.A. River, and FoLAR.
  - Memorabilia (Box 93, Box 94)
    Box 93: Materials include photographs, slides, Los Angeles River Keepers art work, L.A. River drawings, photo copies of historic river images, "Touch the Water" file, and audiovisual materials such as a FoLAR Public Service Announcement and a Master L.A. River performance tape.
    Box 94: Plaques and certificates.
    - The L.A. River, 1985 September; yrlsc_2289_093_006; MacAdams, Lewis; Deluise, Armand; Susan, Marc; Cohen, Lisa; Allora Productions; EZTV; Emigre Graphics; 1 video recordings (1 U-matic; Duration: 0:06:35) (Box 93, Case 6)
      CONTAINS AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS: Audiovisual materials are available for access. All requests to access digital materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
      Transcribed from container: "Master L.A. River"
- Performance materials
  - Taos Poetry Circus files (Box 95, Folder 1-13)
    Files include Battle of the Bards materials and TPC programs, press, notes, and correspondence.
  - Olympic Poetry Festival files (Box 96, Folder 1-7)
    Files include articles, correspondence, attendee lists, and performance agreements.
  - Performance files (Box 97, Folder 4, Box 96, Folder 8-20)
    Box 96: Files include Beyond Baroque, PEN, Allen Ginsberg: Celebration of Life, Bisbee Poetry Festival, Naropa Institute, Performing Tree, workshop and art exhibition materials.
    Box 97, folder 4: Performance programs.
  - Performance flyers and posters (Box 97, Folder 1-3, Box 88, Folder 2, Box 61)
    Box 61: Posters for the following: California Arts Council – A writer for everyone, Art LA '89 – 4th Int'l Contemporary Art Fair, Vittorio Sella Summit and P70 One World Poetry Amsterdam.
    Box 88, folder 2: Posters for events featuring MacAdams and others. This folder includes a San Francisco Poetry Center poster designed by Johanna Drucker.
    Box 97: Files include Lewis MacAdams flyers and posters as well as others such as X, Tim Miller, Dark Bob, and Dennis Cooper.
  - Programs (Box 98, Folder 1-2)
  - Photographs (Box 98, Folder 3-5)
  - Lannan Foundation files (Box 99, Box 100, Box 101, Box 102, Box 103, Box 104, Box 105)
    Box 99 contains administrative files for the Lannan Literary series.
    Boxes 100-105: Lannan Literary Series VHS tapes.
    Box 99, folder 6: One Beirut 7 inch record with Lewis, Dark Bob, and others.
    Box 100: Thirteen VHS
    Box 101: Thirteen VHS
    Box 102: Thirteen VHS
    Box 103: Thirteen VHS
    Box 104: Thirteen VHS
    Box 105: Thirteen VHS
  - Audiovisual materials (Box 106, Box 107, Box 108)
    Audiovisual materials for Tao Poetry Circus.
    Box 106: Two U-Matic tapes, 9 VHS tapes, and 1 Betamax tape.
    Box 107: Three VHS tapes, 19 CDs, 1 Beirut 7-inch LP record (45).
    Box 108: Forty-one audio cassettes.
- Publications (Box 109, Box 110, Box 111, Box 112, Box 113, Box 114, Box 115, Box 116, Box 117, Box 118, Box 119, Box 120)
  Books collected by Lewis MacAdams that were donated with his papers have been individually cataloged in the UCLA Library online catalog. Records for these items may be found by searching the Special Coll/Archive SPAC "LMAC" using the Advanced search tab in the Library catalog, or keyword searching "Books from the Library of Lewis MacAdams."
  - The Library of Lewis MacAdams
    Books from Lewis MacAdams' library that were originally donated with the papers have been individually cataloged in the UCLA Library online catalog. Records for these items may be found by searching the Special Coll/Archive SPAC "LMAC" using the Advanced search tab in the Library catalog, or keyword searching "Books from the library of Lewis MacAdams."
- Memorabilia
  - Family ephemera (Box 121, Box 122, Box 123, Box 130, Folder 1, 5-6)
    Files include Bolinas Life, Hearsay News, divorce paperwork, art created by his kids, Foster Child Advocate Services (FOCAS), and material related St. Mark's School in Dallas.
    Box 130: Paradise Valley Environmental Impact Report, two copies of The Best Harvard Plays books of 1988-1989 with monographs for Lewis and Lee MacAdams.
    Box 123, folder 2: One 3.5 inch floppy disk.
  - Photographs (Box 130, Folder 3, Box 124, Box 125, Box 126)
    Photographs of friends, family, and life in Bolinas.
    Box 126 contains photos of MacAdams and includes his baby book.
    Box 130: Oversize black and white photo of MacAdams in Bolinas.
    Box 124: Two VHS tapes.
  - Plaques (Box 127, Folder 1-7)
    Plaques commemorate MacAdams and his family.
  - Address books (Box 128, Folder 1-10)
    Materials include planners and calendars.
  - Identification cards (Box 129, Folder 1-3)
    Materials include badges, business cards, and buttons.
  - Certificates (Box 130, Folder 2, Box 129, Folder 4)
    Awards and commendations.
  - Memorial materials (Box 129, Folder 5-7)
    Lesley Gilb Taplin, Jim Carroll, and Joanne Kyger.
    Box 129, folder 5: Two Lesley Gilb Taplin family DVDs.
  - Ephemera (Box 129, Folder 8-9)
    Materials include a Nudie's one sheet, a George Foreman vs. Muhammad Ali World Heavyweight Championship ticket, a Hubert Gerold Brown Wanted by the FBI poster, Californians for BROWN (1978) bumper stickers, a ZZ Top caricature of the band signed by Billy Gibbons, and Cops Bust Gangster - Heap No Good! bumper stickers from Jessica Hagedorn and the Gangster Choir at the Poetry Center, San Francisco.
  - Artwork (Box 129, Folder 10-23, Box 88, Folder 3)
    Box 88 contains a We Remember the Hands of the Generations/Recordamos las Manos de las Generaciones poster in support of the College Dream Fund.
    Box 129 includes a Rauschenberg flag, bicycle screen print, Edmund Shea poster, Kora in Hell revisionist project, ballpoint ink drawings, Solidarity Vietnam piece, Lewis' 60th birthday art, and Japanese colored paper.
  - Family recordings (Box 131)
    Materials include recordings of Rhea, Marjorie, Marion MacAdams, Ocean Lee, Willie Blaze, Phoebe, Kyle, and Seth. This box also includes a River Boy t-shirt.
    - Marjorie MacAdams, undated; yrlsc_2289_131_005; 1 sound recordings (1 CD; Duration: 0:28:36) (Box 131, Case 5)
      Transcribed from CD: "Marjorie MacAdams 1 track"
    - Marion MacAdams, undated; yrlsc_2289_131_004; 1 sound recordings (1 CD; Duration: 0:30:11) (Box 131, Case 4)
      Transcribed from CD: "Marion MacAdams CD 2 (1 track)"
    - Marion MacAdams, 2002 November 30; yrlsc_2289_131_003; MacAdams, Will; 1 sound recordings (1 CD; Duration: 0:31:39) (Box 131, Case 3)
      Transcribed from CD: "Marion MacAdams CD 1 (1 track)"
    - Rhea, undated; yrlsc_2289_131_002; 1 sound recordings (1 CD; Duration: 0:22:22) (Box 131, Case 2)
      Transcribed from CD: "Rhea CD 2 (1 Track)"
    - Rhea MacAdams, undated; yrlsc_2289_131_001_01; 1 sound recordings (1 CD; Duration: 0:28:00) (Box 131, Case 1)
      Transcribed from CD: "Rhea MacAdams CD1 (3 Tracks)"
    - Rhea MacAdams, undated; yrlsc_2289_131_001_02; 1 sound recordings (1 CD; Duration: 0:28:00) (Box 131, Case 1)